Guide to the Ronald Reis photographs, 1954-2014 RL.01078
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Negatives, 1954-1976 and undated
  - 1964 October, New York City, Strip D, Greenwich Village, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 October, Strip A, Motorcycle hill climb, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 October, Strip B, Motorcycle hill climb, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 November, New Haven, CT, Strip E, New Haven street scenes (inc. in show), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1964 December, Strip G, Fire at Reilly's Rest (one photo in collection), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 January, Strip C, "8A in Collection?", 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 February, New Haven, CT, Strip E, Yale students rally -- Vietnam (New Haven Green), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 March, London, Strip G, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 March, London, Strip H, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 March, London, Strip J, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 March, London, Strip K, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 March, London, Strip O, Happy Wanderers included, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 March, London, Strip P, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 March, London, Strip Q, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 April, New York City, Strip B, NYC candids, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 October, Strip A, Flea market on Boulevard, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1965 October, West Haven, CT, Strip B, Pamela -- Savin Rock buildings, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - 1967 April, Greece, Strip E, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1967 April, Greece, Strip J, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1967 April, Spain, Strip H, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1967 November, Strip A; Peace demonstration Greenwich Village; celebration of end of Vietnam War, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1968 April, London, Strip E, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1968 April, London, Strip F, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1969 July, London, Strip C, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1969 July, London, Strip D, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1969 July, London, Strip E, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1969 July, London, Strip F (II), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1969 October, New York City, Strip D, Vietnam moratorium (Bryant Park), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1969 October, New York City, Strip E, Vietnam moratorium (Bryant Park), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1970 August, New York City, Strip C, Women's Liberation Day (Bryant Park), 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1972 August, Jerusalem, Strip A, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1972 August, Jerusalem, Strip B, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1974 August, England, Strip A; antique fair, family, England, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1972 August, England, Strip B, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - 1976 January, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - City 8 Keansburg, undated, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous A, undated, 35 mm (Box 8)
  - Miscellaneous B, undated, 120 mm (Box 8)
  - R. Reis fooling around with camera, 1960s?, 120 mm (Box 8)
- Manuscript and Print Materials, 1964-2013; 2 boxes
  Contains a short biographical narrative; curriculum vitae; correspondence from publishers and a museum; publications featuring Reis's photographic work; and publicity relating to Reis's exhibitions and lectures. Also includes a folder with samples of Reis's original negative envelopes with handwritten titles and dates. Folders arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Biographical information, 1964-2012 (Box 7)
  - Camera 35, 1973 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - High Meadows, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Leica Photography, 1985 (2 copies) (Box 7)
  - Original negative envelopes (samples), various years (Box 7)
  - Promotionals, clippings, 1964-2011 (Box 7)
  - Publicity and other papers, 1964-2013 (Box 26)
  - U.S. Camera and Travel, 1964 (Box 7)
  - U.S. Camera International Pictures, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Worcester Art Museum Bulletin, 1974 (2 copies) (Box 7)